<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>English on Hugo-HT</title><link>https://darknessyzy.github.io/tags/english/</link><description>Recent content in English on Hugo-HT</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 13:37:57 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://darknessyzy.github.io/tags/english/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Markdown Testing</title><link>https://darknessyzy.github.io/en/2021/01/07/second-post/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 13:37:57 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://darknessyzy.github.io/en/2021/01/07/second-post/</guid><description>See the source code of this page if you are interested.
H1 H2 H3 H4 H5 H6 List Water Water Water Water Water Water Water Water Water Water Water Water Table Water Water Water Water Water Water Water Water1 Water Water Water Water Quotes What I cannot create, I do not understand2.</description></item><item><title>Daily Life</title><link>https://darknessyzy.github.io/en/1/01/01/daily-life/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://darknessyzy.github.io/en/1/01/01/daily-life/</guid><description>My takeaway from Physics Quantum Cryptography Explained by Professor Dirk Bouwmeester When Biology meets Physics Lectured by Professor Cyrus R. Safinya &amp;#39;Explosion is the key!&amp;#39; Electromagnetism My best friends in Physics: Rio Shiihara and Blake Haist Lab in 9pm First-time internship at SWFC, Shanghai Photo by best friend Sam Cai (summer 2017)!</description></item><item><title>Fun!!!</title><link>https://darknessyzy.github.io/en/1/01/01/fun/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://darknessyzy.github.io/en/1/01/01/fun/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Never give up!!!&amp;#39; Dr.B&amp;#39;s office Why Physics Optical Theory Is there a dinosaur on the blackboard? The world entirely changed after taking a short nap in class. Thermal Magician An Introduction to Thermal Physics by Daniel V. Schroeder My friends: Andy Wang and &amp;#39;Captain Chung&amp;#39; are demonstrating topology to me, by circuits.</description></item><item><title>My Biology Career</title><link>https://darknessyzy.github.io/en/1/01/01/my-biology-career/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://darknessyzy.github.io/en/1/01/01/my-biology-career/</guid><description>Rothman Lab, MCDB Department Where I worked for 2 years! Me in Summer 2018! C. elegans (nematodes) are raised here in sealed plates. Each plate is denoted with date and temperature preserved, and C. elegans&amp;#39; type. Synchronize C. elegans embryos. Design chemotaxis experiments and examine social behavior of C.</description></item><item><title>Physics Experiments (2019)</title><link>https://darknessyzy.github.io/en/1/01/01/physics-experiments-2019/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://darknessyzy.github.io/en/1/01/01/physics-experiments-2019/</guid><description>Electrons (blue laser) are balanced with gravitational force Photo by my lab teammate: Tairan Zhang Five hours a day, four days a week. No more Electronic circuits and bread board!! &amp;lsquo;Labmade&amp;rsquo; cell phone amplifier Try Latex in the command window. Latex output International Space Station (ISS) catched by my teammate Yihong Xu&amp;#39;s iphone camera!</description></item><item><title>Physics Experiments (2020)</title><link>https://darknessyzy.github.io/en/1/01/01/physics-experiments-2020/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://darknessyzy.github.io/en/1/01/01/physics-experiments-2020/</guid><description>The Cavendish Experiment Measured the gravitational constant by the torsional balance equipment (with my friend/teammate Rohit Penumarti)! Movement of pendulum is recorded by camera and fitted on Matlab It takes several hours to wait until the pendulum setting down: it seems damping accidently due to external force. We got perfect data of oscillation and fitted by fourier function on the last day.</description></item></channel></rss>